Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  - Subseries V.E. Miscellaneous, 1978-2004; 5.7 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    - Fortune Perot Poll: Tonight Show, 1992 June 9 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Tonight Show Fortune Poll RE: Perot WNBC T.V. New York 6-9-92 11:30pm Length 4 min.". On label on case side: "Tonight Show Fortune Perot Poll 6-9-92".
    - Fortune/Timberland AD, 1993 September 9 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (5 min., 35 sec.): On label on cassette top: "'Magazine 'Nude' ads' 9 News 9/9/93, WWOR, 10:00p.m. (5:35)". On label on cassette side: "Fortune/Timberland AD 9/9/93".
    - Fortune Junior Achievement: Hall of Fame: 20th Anniversary, 1994 April (Offsite-box 2941, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case front and cassette: "NBHC 20th Hall of Fame Video April 1994". On label on case side: "Fortune Junior Achievement 4-94 Hall of Fame -20th Anniversary V0415". On sticker on case side: "#V0415".
    - Fortune Goes Bi-Weekly: Magazine Productions: New Fortune, 1994 June 2 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 6)
      1 videocassatte (VHS) (17 min., 50 sec.): 1/2 in. On label on case front: "Magazine Productions "New Fortune" TRT 17:50 6/2/94 Fortune Goes Biweekly". On label on case side: "Fortune Goes Biweekly 6/2/94". On label on cassette: "Magazine Productions "New Fortune" TRT 17:50 6/2/94".
    - Fortune Goes Bi-Weekly: Magazine Productions: New Fortune, 1994 June 2 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (17 min., 50 sec.): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Magazine Productions "New Fortune" TRT 17:50 6/2/94 Fortune Goes Biweekly". On label on case side: "New Fortune (goes biweekly) 6/2/94". On label on cassette: "Magazine Productions "New Fortune" TRT 17:50 6/2/94 ".
    - Fortune Magazine References: President Clinton's New Conference: ABC-TV, 1994 August 3 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 30 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine References' Pres. Clinton's New Conference, White House, Aug. 3rd ABC-TV Network August 3rd, 1994 8:00-9:30 PM ET 2:30". On label on case side: "August 3, 1994 - President Clinton's News Conference ABC-TV Network 8:00-9:00 p.m. 2:30".
    - Kramer and Fortune: Seinfeld: NBC-TV, 1994 October 6 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 34 sec.): On label on case front: "8 "Kramer and Fortune Magazine/Seinfeld" Seinfeld NBC-TV Network October 6, 1994 9:00-9:30 PM ET 1:34". On label on case side: "10/6/94 -- Seinfeld -- NBC-TV 1:34 Kramers asks about Fortune". On label on cassette: "'Kramer and Fortune Magazine/Seinfeld' Seinfeld NBC-TV Network October 6, 1994 9:00-9:30 PM ET 1:34". Sticker on cassette side: "10".
    - Jerry at the Dentist's Office: Seinfeld: NBC-TV, 1995 March 16 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (30 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Jerry at the Dentist's Office' Seinfeld NBC-TV Network March 16, 1995 9:00-9:30 PM ET 0:30". On label on case side: "'Jerry at the Dentist's Offie Seinfeld NBC-TV Network 3/16/95 9:00 PM ET 0:30".
    - The Fortune Re-Design Video, 1996 September 9 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case: "The Fortune Re-Design Video Sept 9, 1996 PAL". On labels on cassette: "The Fortune Re-Design Video Sept 9, 1996".
    - The Fortune Re-Design Video, 1996 September 9 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette: "The Fortune Re-Design Video Sept 9, 1996".
    - The Fortune Re-Design Video, 1996 September 9 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 3)
    - The Fortune Re-Design Video, 1996 September 9 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 4)
    - Fortune: In Memoriam: ABC News, 2004 October 24 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (Betacam SP Large) (10 min., 30 sec.): On label on case front: "Story This Week Time 1030 Date 10-24-04". On label on case side: "Fortune In Memoriam 10/24/04 ABC News". On label on cassette: "Story This Week Location CR-B 1030 Date 10-24-04".
    - Fortune: In Memoriam: ABC News, 2004 October 24 (Offsite-box 2942, Folder 1)
      Originally enclosed with Box 2942 Item 5. Folder contains a note from Katie Hinman to Bill telling him about a cassette that was being sent to him.
    - In Memoriam, 2004 October 31 (Offsite-box 2942, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "thisweek Show: In Memoriam Air Date: 10.31.2004". On label on case side: "thisweek Fortune Show: In Memoriam Air Date: 10.31.2004".
    - Fortune Magazine Commercials, undated (Offsite-box 2942, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case and cassette front: "Fortune Magazine Commercials Sample Program Commercial Title (:10) Today Show School Reforms WABC News Titanic WCBS News Raider Good Morning America No Tomorrow". On label on cassette side: "Date? Fortune Magazine Commercials".
    - Fortune Coverage: NBC: The Gay 90s, undated (Offsite-box 2942, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): Written on case: "NBC: The Gay 90s". On label on cassette: "Fortune Coverage Date? NBC Media Relations After 10 Dats please return to Elizabeth McDermott Room 1420, 30 Rockefeller Plaza, N.Y., NY 10112 1st Person..The Gay 90s".
    - Fortune Promotion: Sun Valley, undated (Offsite-box 2942, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Promotion "Sun Valley" Edited 3/4" DUB". On label on case side: "Fortune "Sun Vally" date?". On label on cassette: "Fortune Promotion 'Sun Valley'".
    - Weeden, Finkle, and Fay: Finlay, undated (Offsite-box 2942, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Weeden, Finkle and Fay 1987 La Quinta undated". On label on cassette: "Tape #2 Finaly".
  - Subseries V.F. Box Labels, 2005; 0.5 Linear feet in 31 folders
    This subseries contains box labels that were placed originally glued to the outside of the audiovisual boxes. Since the labels were beginning to fall off, the labels were removed from the boxes and placed in folders within their original box. The labels have information about the original contents of the box as well as information about the transfer of the boxes from their original department to Time Inc.'s archives.
    Arranged chronlogically.
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2911, Folder 2)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2912, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2913, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2914, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2915, Folder 2)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2916, Folder 2)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2917, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2918, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2919, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2920, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2921, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2922, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2923, Folder 2)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2924, Folder 6)
    - Fortune Editors on TV: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2925, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Satellite Press Tours: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2926, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Satellite Press Tours: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2927, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Satellite Press Tours: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2928, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Satellite Press Tours: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2929, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2930, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2931, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2932, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2933, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2934, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2935, Folder 1)
    - Fortune Week and Wall Street Week with Fortune: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2936, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Audiovisual: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2937, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Audiovisual: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2938, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Audiovisual: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2939, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Audiovisual: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2941, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Audiovisual: Box Labels, 2005 July (Offsite-box 2942, Folder 2)